



PERSONAL INFO

EMAIL DATE OF BIRTH GITHUB

hotequil@protonmail.com 2002-06-28 https://github.com/hotequil

LINKEDIN PLACE OF BIRTH WEBSITE

https://www.linkedin.com/in/joao- Gaspar, Santa Catarina, Brazil https://hotequil.tech

paulo-hotequil

I have been working in the Information Technology field since I was 14 years old, starting with hardware and transitioning to software at 16. I maintain a consistent study routine, enhancing my skills through courses, certifications, projects, books, and lectures. I believe in the potential of technology as a tool for decentralization, cost reduction, and improving daily life. I am curious and focused, exploring various areas to apply technological solutions. I prioritize accessibility, responsiveness, performance, semantics, SEO, usability, testing, YAGNI, KISS, security, and quality and design standards.

WORK HISTORY

Front-end Developer

Performa_IT, Home Office

2021-10 - present

As a front-end developer, I work on e-commerce platforms, crowdfunding sites, clients in the financial market, and various systems. I have refactored screens for new technologies, integrated ChatGPT and Pix, and implemented impact credit functionalities and Design Systems. I actively participate in Scrum rituals, collaborate with QAs and designers, and mitigate security issues. Technologies I have used include: React, NextJS, ViteJS, TypeScript, Storybook, SASS, Styled Components, EmotionJS, Chakra UI, Ariakit, Animate.css, polished, Netlify, Zustand, Yarn, Axios, Rollbar, Husky, ESLint, Prettier, GraphQL, SonarQube, Hasura, and NodeJS. I have improved project architectures and implemented file minification pipelines. I prioritize user experience and teamwork, contributing to product quality and innovation. I taught a workshop about Storybook and Web Accessibility for my coworkers.

Front-end Developer

Velow Systems, Blumenau, Santa Catarina, Brazil

I worked as a front-end developer, creating and maintaining web applications, including a corporate social network. I used technologies such as HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, NPM, Git, Material Design, Web Socket, Firebase Web Push Notifications, Service Worker, RxJS, AngularJS, and Angular. I contributed to the implementation of HTTP2, developed an Angular Library for the Design System, and trained new team members.

IT Support

2017-05 - 2018-10

2019-05 - 2021-09

Fazzenda Park Hotel, Gaspar, Santa Catarina, Brazil

I worked as IT Support, managing a high volume of service orders and multiple responsibilities. I gained extensive experience in hardware, networking, and computer maintenance, efficiently resolving technical issues.

EDUCATION

Information Systems

2021-01 - present

FIAF

Upon entering college, I gained extensive experience with languages, libraries, and frameworks such as Python, C, JavaScript, Kotlin, Swift, PostgreSQL, OracleDB, Angular, and React. I studied project management,

UI/UX design, Digital Accessibility, Azure Cloud, and DevOps culture. This learning formed the basis for developing projects including assembling a robot using Arduino, creating an intuitive game for children, developing a supply chain management system, and designing an app for drivers to request mechanical

AWARDS

1st place in NEXT (FIAP)	2022-10
2nd place in NEXT (FIAP)	2023-10
COURSES	
FIAP 60 hours.	2021-10
Front-end programmer Apex 120 hours.	2019-06
NodeJS, TypeScript, TDD, DDD, Clean Architecture e SOLID Udemy 47.5 hours.	2023-07
Web Accessibility developer Alura 20 hours.	2020-04
Full stack (VueJ, GraphQL and NodeJS) Rodrigo Branas 3.5 hours.	2022-01
Front-end formation Alura 360 hours.	2020-11
CERTIFICATES	
Microsoft 70-480 Microsoft	2020-12
VueJS (gold) TestDome	2022-01
NodeJS (gold) TestDome	2022-01
JavaScript (gold) TestDome	2022-01

Alura

SKILLS

- Hard Skills: React, Angular, AngularJS, NextJS, ViteJS, Vue, JavaScript, TypeScript, GraphQL, Storybook, RxJS, HTML, CSS, SASS, Styled Components, Prettier, Husky, ESLint, Chakra UI, Ariakit, Yarn, ES6+, Axios, Animate.css, NodeJS, Netlify e Zustand.
- Soft Skills: Communication, continuous improvement, autonomy, proactivity, conflict resolution, collaboration, leadership, active participation, teamwork, task management, adaptability, and time management.

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese C2
- English B1

VOLUNTEERING

Movimento Web Para Todos

2024-02 - present

At the "Liga Voluntária", I volunteer for the "Movimento Web para Todos", actively contributing to the transformation of the Brazilian web into a much fairer, inclusive, and accessible environment for all people.